<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="com.st.flexperf.binutils.feature"
      label="STProfiler Binary Tools Feature"
      version="6.2.0.201206291358"
      provider-name="STMicroelectronics">

   <description>
      This feature brings support for common binary utilities such
as link to source, file checksum, nm, addr2line, ...
   </description>

   <copyright>
      (C) 2010 STMicroelectronics ALL RIGHTS RESERVED
This program contains proprietary information and is not to be
used, copied, nor disclosed without the written consent of STMicroelectronics.
   </copyright>

   <license url="ela.html">
      SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT (THE “AGREEMENT”)
IMPORTANT - READ CAREFULLY: NOTICE: PLEASE READ THIS AGREEMENT
CAREFULLY BEFORE DOWNLOADING, COPYING OR USING THE LICENSED MATERIALS.
THIS SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT IS A LEGAL AGREEMENT BETWEEN
YOU, THE LICENSEE (A SINGLE PERSON, INSTITUTION, OR LEGAL ENTITY
EXERCISING RIGHTS UNDER THIS EULA. FOR LEGAL ENTITIES “YOU” INCLUDES
ANY ENTITY THAT IS CONTROLLED BY YOU WHERE CONTROL MEANS OWNERSHIP
OF MORE THAN FIFTY PERCENT OF THE OUTSTANDING SHARES OR BENEFICIAL
OWERSHIP OF SUCH ENTITY), AND STMICROELECTRONICS N.V. A COMPANY
ORGANIZED UNDER THE LAW OF NETHERLANDS WITH ITS REGISTERED OFFICE
AT WTC SCHIPHOL AIRPORT, SCHIPHOL BOULEVARD 265, 1118 BH SCHIPHOL
AIRPORT, AMSTERDAM, THE NETHERLANDS, ACTING THROUGH ITS SWISS
BRANCH LOCATED AT 39, CHEMIN DU CHAMP DES FILLES, 1228 PLAN-LES-OUATES,
GENEVA, SWITZERLAND (“ST”), FOR THE SOFTWARE, AND ELECTRONIC
DOCUMENTATION OR ANY PORTION THEREOF (THE “LICENSED MATERIALS”).
BY INSTALLING AND USING THE LICENSED MATERIALS ACCOMPANYING THIS
SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT INDICATES YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE
TERMS AND CONDITIONS. THE LICENSED MATERIALS ARE ELECTRONICALLY
DISTRIBUTED AND ARE COMPOSED OF THE FOLLOWING COMPONENTS THAT
CONTAIN SOFTWARE CODE:
1. COMPONENTS INCLUDED IN THE DIRECTORIES \stworkbench\features\org.eclipse.&lt;id&gt;.&lt;id&gt;…&lt;id&gt;,\stworkbench\plugins\org.eclipse.&lt;id&gt;.&lt;id&gt;…&lt;id&gt;
AND ASSOCIATED SUBDIRECTORIES, IF ANY, (HEREAFTER “Directories
1”) ARE SUBJECT TO THE ECLIPSE PUBLIC LICENSE V1.0 ATTACHED TO
THIS AGREEMENT AS APPENDIX 2;
2. COMPONENTS INCLUDED IN THE DIRECTORIES \stworkbench\features\,
\stworkbench\plugins\ AND ASSOCIATED SUBDIRECTORIES, IF ANY,
NAMED org.eclipse.&lt;id&gt;.&lt;id&gt;…&lt;id&gt; (HEREAFTER “Directories 2”)ARE
SUBJECT TO THE ECLIPSE PUBLIC LICENSE V1.0 ATTACHED TO THIS AGREEMENT
AS APPENDIX 2;
3. PROPRIETARY COMPONENTS INCLUDED IN THE DIRECTORIES \stworkbench\features\com.st.&lt;id&gt;.&lt;id&gt;…&lt;id&gt;,
\stworkbench\plugins\com.st.&lt;id&gt;.&lt;id&gt;…&lt;id&gt; AND ASSOCIATED SUBDIRECTORIES,
IF ANY, (HEREAFTER “Directories 3”) ARE SUBJECT TO THE TERMS
SET FORTH IN APPENDIX 1 BELOW.
4. PROPRIETARY COMPONENTS INCLUDED IN THE DIRECTORIES \stworkbench\features\,
\stworkbench\plugins\ AND ASSOCIATED SUBDIRECTORIES, IF ANY,
NAMED com.st.&lt;id&gt;.&lt;id&gt;…&lt;id&gt; (HEREAFTER “Directories 4”) ARE SUBJECT
TO THE TERMS SET FORTH IN APPENDIX 1 BELOW.
IMPORTANT -- READ CAREFULLY: BY CLICKING ON THE AGREE BUTTON
YOU AGREE TO BE AND ARE HEREBY BOUND BY THE TERMS OF THIS SOFTWARE
LICENSE AGREEMENT. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS, PRESS DISAGREE
BUTTON AND MUST PROMPTLY DESTROY ALL COPIES OF THE SOFTWARE YOU
MAY HAVE RECEIVED OR DOWNLOADED.
Appendix 1
Terms and Conditions
1.1 The proprietary software delivered to You under this Agreement
is described in the Directories 1 and Directories 2 is in form
of source code and/or executable code. The proprietary software,
including the documentation, if and when provided, and any updates
(collectively referred to as the “Proprietary Software”) furnished
to You are proprietary to LICENSOR or its licensor (ST and licensors
hereafter refers to as &quot;Licensor&quot;). Licensor retains title to
and ownership of the Proprietary Software, including the copy
provided herein, and reserves all rights not expressly granted
in this Agreement. You assume responsibility for the selection
of the Proprietary Software to achieve your intended results,
and for the installation, use and results obtained from the Proprietary
Software.
1.2 Under the terms and conditions of this Agreement, and in
particular subject to the restrictions and other terms within
this Appendix 1, You are hereby granted a limited, revocable,
nontransferable and nonexclusive worldwide, license to use the
source code of the Proprietary Software to develop software application
and to use, copy, distribute, license in object code form only
such software application solely and only in conjunction with
the Target Hardware set forth in the Table above. Such foregoing
right must be (i) only by or for You, and (ii) only for the Target
Hardware. Any other use of the Proprietary Software is strictly
prohibited.
1.3 You have the right to use contractors provided that You (a)
unconditionally guarantee the performance of Your contractor
in connection with Your obligations set forth in this Agreement
and the compliance of Your contractor with the terms and conditions
of this Agreement, (b) agree to indemnify LICENSOR against all
and any loss, liability, costs, damages, expenses (including
the fees of lawyers and other professionals), suffered, incurred
or sustained as a result of or in relation to the breach of the
terms of this Agreement.
1.4 Any copy of the Proprietary Software shall include the copyright
notice and other proprietary legends indicated on the Proprietary
Software. Except as set forth in Section 1.2 above, You may not
modify, adapt, translate, reverse engineer, de-compile, disassemble,
or create derivative works in whole or in part based on the Proprietary
Software. You may not rent, lease, loan, or electronically transfer
the Proprietary Software to others or from one computer to another
over a network.
1.5 The term &quot;proprietary&quot; as used in this agreement does not
establish a confidential relationship between the Licensor and
You. You will respect all intellectual property rights, in particular
copyrights, and patents that the Licensor has in the Proprietary
Software. You agree that normal usage of the Proprietary Software
by You will not violate Licensor&apos;s proprietary rights. IF YOU
OTHERWISE TRANSFER POSSESSION OF ANY COPY, OF ANY MODIFICATION
OR OF ANY MERGED PORTION OF THE PROPRIETARY SOFTWARE TO ANOTHER
PARTY, YOUR LICENSE IS AUTOMATICALLY TERMINATED.
1.6 Licensor represents that the ideas and expressions contained
in the Proprietary Software (but not the executable form of the
Proprietary Software, in which those ideas and expressions are
encrypted) are confidential proprietary information of Licensor
(“Licensor Confidential Information”) in which You have no interest
and no right to use, other than as granted by this Appendix 1.
You acknowledge that unauthorized copying or disclosure of Licensor
Confidential Information may cause irreparable injury to Licensor
and that Licensor shall be entitled to, among other actions,
seek to enjoin such activities. You shall have an appropriate
agreement with each of its employees having access to Licensor
Confidential Information, sufficient to enable You to comply
with all terms of this Appendix 1.
Information shall not be considered to be Confidential Information
if it: (1) is already or otherwise becomes publicly known through
no act of the other party; (2) is lawfully received from third
parties subject to no restriction of confidentiality; or (3)
can be shown by You to have been independently developed by You
without reference to the Confidential Information. You will keep
the Confidential Information in confidence and trust during the
term of this Appendix 1 and for five (5) years after termination,
and You will not use the Confidential Information other than
as permitted under this Appendix 1.
1.7 THE PROPRIETARY SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &quot;AS IS&quot; WITHOUT WARRANTY
OF ANY KIND. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW,
Licensor FURTHER DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION
ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR
PURPOSE, AND NONINFRINGEMENT. THE ENTIRE RISK ARISING OUT OF
THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THE PROPRIETARY SOFTWARE AND DOCUMENTATION
REMAINS WITH YOU. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE
LAW. IN NO EVENT SHALL Licensor BE LIABLE FOR ANY CONSEQUENTIAL,
INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, OR OTHER DAMAGES WHATSOEVER
DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF BUSINESS PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION,
LOSS OF BUSINESS INFORMATION, LOSS OF DATA OR OTHER PECUNIARY
LOSS, ARISING OUT OF THIS Agreement OR THE USE OF OR INABILITY
TO USE THE PROPRIETARY SOFTWARE, EVEN IF Licensor HAS BEEN ADVISED
OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. BECAUSE SOME STATES/JURISDICTIONS
DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL
OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO
YOU. NOTWITHSTANDING THE FOREGOING, TO THE EXTENT THAT Licensor
MAY BE HELD LEGALLY LIABLE TO YOU BY A COURT OF COMPETENT JURISDICTION
UNDER CONTRACT, TORT, OR ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY, THE MAXIMUM
LIABILITY OF Licensor SHALL NOT EXCEED ONE HUNDRED US DOLLARS
($100.00). BECAUSE SOME STATES/JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE
EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL
DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
1.8 The documentations(s), if any, provided with the Proprietary
Software is copyrighted and may not be copied, photographed,
reproduced, translated or reduced to any electronic medium or
machine-readable form in whole or in part.
1.9 The Proprietary Software is a &quot;commercial item,&quot; as that
term is defined at 48 C.F.R. 2.101 (OCT 1995), consisting of
&quot;commercial computer software&quot; and &quot;commercial computer software
documentation,&quot; as such terms are used in 48 C.F.R. 12.212 (SEPT
1995) and is provided to the U.S. Government only as a commercial
end item. Consistent with 48 C.F.R. 12.212 and 48 C.F.R. 227.7202-1
through 227.7202-4 (JUNE 1995), all U.S. Government licensees
and end users acquire the Software with only those rights set
forth herein.
1.10 The license of the Proprietary Software is effective until
terminated. You may terminate it at any time by returning and/or
destroying the Proprietary Software together with all copies.
This license of the Proprietary Software will also terminate
immediately without notice from Licensor If You fail to comply
with any provision of Appendix 1 of this Agreement. You must
return the original Proprietary Software and any copies, including
any updates, upon termination of this Agreement.
1.11 You agree that the Proprietary Software shall not be exported
or re-exported, directly or indirectly, to any destination restricted
or prohibited by export control regulations without the required
authorization or license from the appropriate governmental or
other regulatory authorities.
1.12 You covenant and agree that You shall not (i) create derivative
works of the Licensed Materials in any manner that would cause
the Licensed Materials, in whole or in part, to become subject
to any of the terms of the Excluded License or (ii) distribute
the Licensed Materials (or derivative works including the Software)
in any manner that would cause any Licensed Materials component
to become subject to any of the terms of the Excluded License.
An “Excluded License” is any license that requires as a condition
of use, modification and/or distribution of software subject
to the Excluded License, that such software or other software
combined and/or distributed with such software be (x) disclosed
or distributed in source code form; (y) licensed for the purpose
of making derivative works; or (z) re-distributable at no charge.
1.13 This Appendix 1 shall be construed and interpreted under
the laws of France, not including conflict of laws principles
of France. If any provision of Appendix 1 of this Agreement,
or portion thereof, is found to be unenforceable, that provision
shall be enforced to the maximum extent possible and the remainder
of this Appendix 1 of this Agreement shall continue in full force
and effect. This is the entire agreement between You and Licensor
with respect to the Proprietary Software and supersedes all prior
or contemporaneous understandings or agreements, written or oral,
regarding such subject matter and may only be modified in writing
executed by LICENSOR and You.
1.14 YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ APPENDIX 1 OF THIS AGREEMENT
AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY ITS TERMS. YOU FURTHER AGREE THAT IT
IS THE COMPLETE AND EXCLUSIVE STATEMENT OF AGREEMENT BETWEEN
US THAT SUPERSEDE ANY PRIOR AGREEMENT, ORAL OR WRITTEN, ANY PROPOSAL
AND ANY OTHER COMMUNICATIONS BETWEEN LICENSOR AND YOU RELATING
TO THE SUBJECT MATTER OF THIS AGREEMENT.
[End of Appendix 1]
Appendix 2
Eclipse Public License – v 1.0
The software subject to this Eclipse Public License v1.0 (the
“License”) is described in the Directories 3 and Directories
4 is in form of source code and/or executable code.
1. DEFINITIONS
- &quot;Contribution&quot; means: (a) in the case of the initial Contributor,
the initial code and documentation distributed under this License,
and (b) in the case of each subsequent Contributor changes to
the Program, and additions to the Program; where such changes
and/or additions to the Program originate from and are distributed
by that particular Contributor. A Contribution &apos;originates&apos; from
a Contributor if it was added to the Program by such Contributor
itself or anyone acting on such Contributor&apos;s behalf. Contributions
do not include additions to the Program which: (i) are separate
modules of software distributed in conjunction with the Program
under their own license agreement, and (ii) are not derivative
works of the Program.
- &quot;Contributor&quot; means any person or entity that distributes the
Program.
- &quot;Licensed Patents&quot; mean patent claims licensable by a Contributor
which are necessarily infringed by the use or sale of its Contribution
alone or when combined with the Program.
- &quot;Program&quot; means the Contributions distributed in accordance
with this License.
- &quot;Recipient&quot; means anyone who receives the Program under this
License, including all Contributors.
2. GRANT OF RIGHTS
2.1 Subject to the terms of this License, each Contributor hereby
grants Recipient a non-exclusive, worldwide, royalty-free copyright
license to reproduce, prepare derivative works of, publicly display,
publicly perform, distribute and sublicense the Contribution
of such Contributor, if any, and such derivative works, in source
code and object code form.
2.2 Subject to the terms of this License, each Contributor hereby
grants Recipient a nonexclusive, worldwide, royalty-free patent
license under Licensed Patents to make, use, sell, offer to sell,
import and otherwise transfer the Contribution of such Contributor,
if any, in source code and object code form. This patent license
shall apply to the combination of the Contribution and the Program
if, at the time the Contribution is added by the Contributor,
such addition of the Contribution causes such combination to
be covered by the Licensed Patents. The patent license shall
not apply to any other combinations which include the Contribution.
No hardware per se is licensed hereunder.
2.3 Recipient understands that although each Contributor grants
the licenses to its Contributions set forth herein, no assurances
are provided by any Contributor that the Program does not infringe
the patent or other intellectual property rights of any other
entity. Each Contributor disclaims any liability to Recipient
for claims brought by any other entity based on infringement
of intellectual property rights or otherwise. As a condition
to exercising the rights and licenses granted hereunder, each
Recipient hereby assumes sole responsibility to secure any other
intellectual property rights needed, if any. For example, if
a third party patent license is required to allow Recipient to
distribute the Program, it is Recipient&apos;s responsibility to acquire
that license before distributing the Program.
2.4 Each Contributor represents that to its knowledge it has
sufficient copyright rights in its Contribution, if any, to grant
the copyright license set forth in this License.
3. REQUIREMENTS
3.1 A Contributor may choose to distribute the Program in object
code form under its own license agreement, provided that (a)
it complies with the terms and conditions of this License, and
(b) its license agreement (i) effectively disclaims on behalf
of all Contributors all warranties and conditions, express and
implied, including warranties or conditions of title and non-infringement,
and implied warranties or conditions of merchantability and fitness
for a particular purpose, (ii) effectively excludes on behalf
of all Contributors all liability for damages, including direct,
indirect, special, incidental and consequential damages, such
as lost profits, (iii) states that any provisions which differ
from this License are offered by that Contributor alone and not
by any other party; and (iv) states that source code for the
Program is available from such Contributor, and informs licensees
how to obtain it in a reasonable manner on or through a medium
customarily used for software exchange.
3.2 When the Program is made available in source code form it
must be made available under this License and a copy of this
License must be included with each copy of the Program.
3.3 Contributors may not remove or alter any copyright notices
contained within the Program.
3.4 Each Contributor must identify itself as the originator of
its Contribution, if any, in a manner that reasonably allows
subsequent Recipients to identify the originator of the Contribution.
4. COMMERCIAL DISTRIBUTION
4.1 Commercial distributors of software may accept certain responsibilities
with respect to end users, business partners and the like. While
this license is intended to facilitate the commercial use of
the Program, the Contributor who includes the Program in a commercial
product offering should do so in a manner which does not create
potential liability for other Contributors. Therefore, if a Contributor
includes the Program in a commercial product offering, such Contributor
(&quot;Commercial Contributor&quot;) hereby agrees to defend and indemnify
every other Contributor (&quot;Indemnified Contributor&quot;) against any
losses, damages and costs (collectively &quot;Losses&quot;) arising from
claims, lawsuits and other legal actions brought by a third party
against the Indemnified Contributor to the extent caused by the
acts or omissions of such Commercial Contributor in connection
with its distribution of the Program in a commercial product
offering. The obligations in this section do not apply to any
claims or Losses relating to any actual or alleged intellectual
property infringement. In order to qualify, an Indemnified Contributor
must: a) promptly notify the Commercial Contributor in writing
of such claim, and b) allow the Commercial Contributor to control,
and cooperate with the Commercial Contributor in, the defense
and any related settlement negotiations. The Indemnified Contributor
may participate in any such claim at its own expense.
4.2 For example, a Contributor might include the Program in a
commercial product offering, Product X. That Contributor is then
a Commercial Contributor. If that Commercial Contributor then
makes performance claims, or offers warranties related to Product
X, those performance claims and warranties are such Commercial
Contributor&apos;s responsibility alone. Under this section, the Commercial
Contributor would have to defend claims against the other Contributors
related to those performance claims and warranties, and if a
court requires any other Contributor to pay any damages as a
result, the Commercial Contributor must pay those damages.
5. NO WARRANTY
5.1 EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY SET FORTH IN THIS AGREEMENT, THE PROGRAM
IS PROVIDED ON AN &quot;AS IS&quot; BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS
OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION,
ANY WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF TITLE, NON-INFRTNGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY
OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. Each Recipient is solely
responsible for determining the appropriateness of using and
distributing the Program and assumes all risks associated with
its exercise of rights under this License, including but not
limited to the risks and costs of program errors, compliance
with applicable laws, damage to or loss of data, programs or
equipment, and unavailability or interruption of operations.
6. DISCLAIMER OF LIABILITY
6.1 EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY SET FORTH IN THIS AGREEMENT, NEITHER
RECIPIENT NOR ANY CONTRIBUTORS SHALL HAVE ANY LIABILITY FOR ANY
DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL
DAMAGES (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION LOST PROFITS), HOWEVER
CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT
LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING
IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OR DISTRIBUTION OF THE PROGRAM OR THE
EXERCISE OF ANY RIGHTS GRANTED HEREUNDER, EVEN IF ADVISED OF
THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
7. GENERAL
7.1 If any provision of this License is invalid or unenforceable
under applicable law, it shall not affect the validity or enforceability
of the remainder of the terms of this License, and without further
action by the parties hereto, such provision shall be reformed
to the minimum extent necessary to make such provision valid
and enforceable.
7.2 If Recipient institutes patent litigation against any entity
(including a cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging
that the Program itself (excluding combinations of the Program
with other software or hardware) infringes such Recipient&apos;s patent(s),
then such Recipient&apos;s rights granted under Section 2(b) shall
terminate as of the date such litigation is Sled.
7.2 All Recipient&apos;s rights under this License shall terminate
if it fails to comply with any of the material terms or conditions
of this License and does not cure such failure in a reasonable
period of time after becoming aware of such noncompliance. If
all Recipient&apos;s rights under this License terminate, Recipient
agrees to cease use and distribution of the Program as soon as
reasonably practicable. However, Recipient&apos;s obligations under
this License and any licenses granted by Recipient relating to
the Program shall continue and survive.
7.3 Everyone is permitted to copy and distribute copies of this
License, but in order to avoid inconsistency the License is copyrighted
and may only be modified in the following manner. The License
Steward reserves the right to publish new versions (including
revisions) of this License from time to time. No one other than
the License Steward has the right to modify this License. The
Eclipse Foundation is the initial License Steward. The Eclipse
Foundation may assign the responsibility to serve as the License
Steward to a suitable separate entity. Each new version of the
License will be given a distinguishing version number. The Program
(including Contributions) may always be distributed subject to
the version of the License under which it was received. In addition,
after a new version of the License is published, Contributor
may elect to distribute the Program (including its Contributions)
under the new version. Except as expressly stated in Sections
2(a) and 2(b) above, Recipient receives no rights or licenses
to the intellectual property of any Contributor under this License,
whether expressly, by implication, estoppel or otherwise. All
rights in the Program not expressly granted under this License
are reserved.
7.4 This License is governed by the laws of the State of New
York and the intellectual property laws of the United States
of America. No party to this License will bring a legal action
under this License more than one year after the cause of action
arose. Each party waives its rights to a jury trial in any resulting
litigation
[End of Appendix 2]
BY AGREEING TO THIS AGREEMENT I REPRESENT AND WARRANT THAT I
AM AN AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVE OF THE LICENSEE.
   </license>

   <plugin
         id="com.st.flexperf.binutils"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="6.2.0.201206291358"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
